Guide to the James B. Hunt Papers
James B. Hunt Papers
1971-1997
1971 1997
Hunt James B. 1937-
MC 00003
The James B. Hunt Papers, 1971-1997, include videotapes, films, audiotapes, photographs, correspondence, news clippings, ad slicks, position papers, advertisement scripts, cue sheets, stickers, buttons, and brochures relating to the political campaigns of James Baxter Hunt Jr., who was a four-term Democratic governor of North Carolina, 1977-1985 and 1993-2001. The largest portion of the collection is the videotapes, which feature television advertisements produced for Hunt’s campaigns, debate preparation sessions, debates, and television news broadcasts about the campaigns. The bulk of these materials document Hunt’s unsuccessful 1984 bid to unseat Republican Jesse Helms as United States Senator from North Carolina and the 1992 gubernatorial campaign, in which Hunt defeated Republican James Gardner. Also included is material relating to his 1996 gubernatorial campaign, and some material from the 1976 and 1980 gubernatorial campaigns. Not included are any materials specifically documenting Hunt’s official acts as governor.
James Baxter Hunt, Jr. (1937- ) was Democratic governor of North Carolina, 1977-1985 and 1993-2001. After serving as Lieutenant Governor from 1973 to 1977, he served two terms as Governor, 1977-1981 and 1981-1985. In 1984 he waged an unsuccessful campaign to unseat Republican Jesse Helms as United States Senator from North Carolina. The closely contested race, which Helms eventually won with 52% of the vote, garnered national attention as both sides engaged in negative campaigning, some of which centered on Hunt’s support for (and Helms’s opposition to) the recognition of Martin Luther King, Jr. Day. The campaign ultimately cost a combined $22 million, making it the most expensive Senate race in American history to that point. Hunt returned to elected office in 1993, winning a third term as Governor by defeating Republican Lieutenant Governor James C. Gardner. In 1996 he was elected to a fourth term over Republican state Representative Robin Hayes. Hunt left office in 2001.
84.7 linear feet
North Carolina State University Libraries, Special Collections Research Center
Collection is open for research; access requires at least 48 hours advance notice. Use copies of videotapes, film, or audiotapes must be made prior to patron viewing or listening.
Gift of James B. Hunt, June 2001 (Accession 2001.0022) and March 2013 (Accession 2013.0055).
This collection is arranged in six series:
Videotape Film Audiotape Photographs Documents Gubernatorial Campaign Materials
James Baxter Hunt, Jr. (1937- ) was Democratic governor of North Carolina, 1977-1985 and 1993-2001. He earned a Bachelor of Science degree in agricultural education and a Master’s degree in agricultural economics from North Carolina State University, where he served two terms as student body president, as well as a Juris Doctorate from the University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill.
After serving as Lieutenant Governor from 1973 to 1977, Hunt served two terms as Governor, 1977-1981 and 1981-1985. In 1984 he waged an unsuccessful campaign to unseat Republican Jesse Helms as United States Senator from North Carolina. The closely contested race, which Helms eventually won with 52% of the vote, garnered national attention as both sides engaged in negative campaigning, some of which centered on Hunt’s support for (and Helms’s opposition to) the recognition of Martin Luther King, Jr. Day. The campaign ultimately cost a combined $22 million, making it the most expensive Senate race in American history to that point. Hunt returned to elected office in 1992, winning a third term as Governor by defeating Republican Lieutenant Governor James C. Gardner. In 1996 he was elected to a fourth term over Republican state Representative Robin Hayes. Hunt left office in 2001.
After he left the governorship, Hunt joined the law firm of Womble Carlyle Sandridge & Rice, PLLC, in Raleigh. As of 2006, he and his wife, Carolyn, lived on their beef cattle farm in eastern North Carolina. They had four children and ten grandchildren.
James B. Hunt, Jr., Papers (#325), East Carolina Manuscript Collection, J. Y. Joyner Library, East Carolina University, Greenville, North Carolina (http://digital.lib.ecu.edu/special/ead/findingaids/0325/)
Governor's Papers -- James Baxter Hunt, Jr. (16 May 1937 --), Record Group 372 and Record Group 374, State Archives of North Carolina, Raleigh, NC
Lieutenant Governor's Papers -- James Baxter Hunt, Jr., Record Group 395, State Archives of North Carolina, Raleigh, NC
The James B. Hunt Papers, 1971-1997, include videotapes, films, audiotapes, photographs, correspondence, news clippings, ad slicks, position papers, advertisement scripts, cue sheets, stickers, buttons, and brochures relating to the political campaigns of James Baxter Hunt Jr., who was a four-term Democratic governor of North Carolina, 1977-1985 and 1993-2001. The largest portion of the collection is the videotapes, which feature television advertisements produced for Hunt’s campaigns, debate preparation sessions, debates, and television news broadcasts about the campaigns. The bulk of these materials document Hunt’s unsuccessful 1984 bid to unseat Republican Jesse Helms as United States Senator from North Carolina and the 1992 gubernatorial campaign, in which Hunt defeated Republican James Gardner. Also included is material relating to his 1996 gubernatorial campaign, and some material from the 1976 and 1980 gubernatorial campaigns. Not included are any materials specifically documenting Hunt’s official acts as governor.
Hunt James B. 1937-; Hunt James B. 1937-; Clippings; Posters; Filmstrips; Video tapes; Audiotapes; North Carolina History 20th century Political campaigns; North Carolina Politics and government 1951-
- Videotape, 1980-1984, 1987-1997, and undated
  This series contain videotapes in a variety of formats: VHS, U-matic, BetaMax, BetaCam, 1" Type C, 2" Quad, and 1/2" open reel. These videotapes feature television commercials produced for Hunt’s campaigns, debate preparation sessions, debates, speeches, and television news broadcasts about the campaigns. Transcripts and cue sheets for some of the commercials may be found in Series 5.
  - General Election Debate, Jim Hunt and Beverly Lake, 1980 September 15 (Box 1)
  - Hunt: 11 spots titles enclosed, 1980 September 24 (Box 1)
  - Baptist State Convention: Prime Minister of Humor, 1981 April 7 (Box 1)
  - Governor Hunt Spot: "Road-102", 1981 June 4 (Box 1)
  - Jim Hunt: International Year of Disabled People 1982 PSA (Box 1)
  - The Light in the Graveyard: The Story of the Hatteras Light, 1982 (Box 1)
  - The Jim Hunter [sic] Committee: 1) Good Roads 2) Bad Road NC, Bad Road NY 3) Economic Development - Indutry/Tourism 4) Repairs & Construction 5) Interviews, 1982 April 24 (Box 1)
  - Burlington Video Network: "Sounding It Out:" Horizons for Learning Videotape, 1982 December 1 (Box 1)
  - Governor Hunt: Statewide DUI Address / Senator Helms: Social Security Address, 1983 January 4 (Box 1)
  - Jesse Helms - Social Security Presentation, 1983 February (Box 2)
  - Hunt Press Conference, 1983 September 20 (Box 1)
  - Jim Hunt - Campaign '84 64, 1984 (Box 8)
  - US vs. USSR, Rickover, The Military Budget, El Salvador, 1984 (Box 8)
  - Governor Hunt TV Ads 1984 (Box 8)
  - 255 - Hunt "Scare Senior Citizens," 275 - NC's Senator Friends of Jesse, [1984?] (Box 8)
  - Helms, Union Label, Helms Reagan / Where do you stand, Jim?, [1984?] (Box 8)
  - Hunt for Senate, Helms Commercials, Ferraro Debate, Dole & It's a Lie, [1984?] (Box 8)
  - 1845 - Mondale/Hunt ten second, 2480 - Helms carspot, [1984?] (Box 8)
  - 2300 Helms ad, National Governors Association, [1984?] (Box 8)
  - Helms commercials, Dole & It's a Lie response, [1984?] (Box 8)
  - Helms Commercials, response to it's a lie, Liddy Dole, Strom Thurmond, Two Minute Spot, Howard Baker, [1984?] (Box 8)
  - Helms school prayer 1163, [1984?] (Box 8)
  - Helms, Charlton Heston 346, [1984?] (Box 8)
  - Helms, It's a Lie response (278) + Dole (290), [1984?] (Box 8)
  - Hunt/Sawyer Prep Sessions, [1984?] (Box 8)
  - Jesse Helms TV Spots, [1984?] (Box 8)
  - Jesse Helms TV Spots, [1984?] (Box 8)
  - Original Dot Helms - 1065, 10 second - "Mondale/Hunt 1827, [1984?] (Box 8)
  - 871 - "Farmer" for Helms, [1984?] (Box 8)
  - 773-Helms "You have my word" soc. Security, 860-Scare-NGA, [1984?] (Box 8)
  - 0003-Helms on FEC probe, [1984?] (Box 8)
  - Hunt - FEC (Helms/fee investigation), [1984?] (Box 8)
  - Helms :30 Hunt N.Y. Comm, [1984?] (Box 9)
  - Helms, Teachers :30, NYC :30, NGA :30, [1984?] (Box 9)
  - Hunt Mrs. Helms Response Spot, [1984?] (Box 9)
  - 1253 - RR Jon Jesse, 1453 - 10 second Mondale/Hunt, [1984?] (Box 9)
  - Hunt Shoot, D'Aubuisson in DC, [1984?] (Box 9)
  - News 6/26-27: Helms, D'Aubuisson, [1984?] (Box 9)
  - Niteline 6/27, D'Aubuisson, Sunday AM 7/1 WTVD 6/27 (Helms Live), [1984?] (Box 9)
  - 5/25 - 5/28, [1984?] (Box 9)
  - 6/19 - 6/22, [1984?] (Box 9)
  - 7/2-7/4: WPTF and WRAL News Segments, [1984?] (Box 9)
  - Helms/Hunt TV, 4/24 - Noon 4/27, [1984?] (Box 9)
  - News 6/26-7/1, [1984?] (Box 9)
  - Hunt News 5/14 - 5/19, [1984?] (Box 9)
  - 5/20 - 5/28, [1984?] (Box 9)
  - Hunt 6/12 - 6/18, [1984?] (Box 9)
  - Hunt TV News Week of 4/30 - 5/4, [1984?] (Box 9)
  - News Clips - Jim Hunt; June 19 (6pm) - June 26 (noon), [1984?] (Box 9)
  - Helms - "Vote/Taxes;" Hunt - "Something Is Wrong (Lies);: Helms - School Prayer;" Hunt - "Enemies," "Dead Last," "Basketball," "Pride", [1984?] (Box 9)
  - Mondale Debate Original #484, [1984?] (Box 9)
  - Hunt News Clips, [1984?] (Box 9)
  - Helms critical of Governor on tornado, [1984?] (Box 9)
  - 7/5 - 7/9, [1984?] (Box 9)
  - Dot Helms 10/31, [1984?] (Box 9)
  - Hunt's early commercials / Compilation of Helms' spots, [1984?] (Box 9)
  - New Dot Helms Ad, [1984?] (Box 9)
  - Mondale/Reagan Tax, [1984?] (Box 9)
  - Helms for Senate ads, [1984?] (Box 9)
  - D'Aubuisson in DC, [1984?] (Box 9)
  - Hunt: Hunt Speech, Film Xfer, 1984 January 30 (Box 1)
  - Hunt Rough TV Spots, 1984 January 30 (Box 1)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-101, "Together;" JHSEN-102, "Together;" JHSEN-103, "Working People;" JHSEN-104, "Working People;" JHSEN-105, "Farmer"`, 1984 February 1 (Box 1)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-101, "Together;" JHSEN-102, "Together;" JHSEN-103, "Working People;" JHSEN-104, "Working People;" JHSEN-105, "Farmer"`, 1984 February 1 (Box 1)
  - Hunt: First North Carolina Shoot, "Future;" "Motive" Film XFER, 1984 February 8 (Box 1)
  - Hunt: First North Carolina Shoot, "Future;" "Motive" Film XFER, 1984 February 8 (Box 1)
  - School Prayer response - Channel 5, 1984 March 7 (Box 2)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-108, "Real Issue", 1984 March 16 (Box 2)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-108, "Real Issue", 1984 March 16 (Box 2)
  - Hunt: A & B Roll (Work Pics), 1984 March 27 (Box 2)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-110, "Fun & Games", 1984 May 7 (Box 2)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-110, "Fun & Games;" JHSEN-111, "Agriculture;" JHSEN-112, "Tax Cuts", 1984 May 16 (Box 2)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-113, "Standing Tall", 1984 May 25 (Box 2)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-114A, "Friends;" JHSEN-114B, "Friends;" JHSEN-115, "Yes", 1984 May 31 (Box 2)
  - Social Issues Group 1, 1984 June 8 (Box 2)
  - Social Issues Group 2, 1984 June 8 (Box 2)
  - Bi2 Net: Ask Washington; Jesse Helms, 1984 June 11 (Box 2)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-116, "Death Squads", 1984 June 25 (Box 2)
  - Delta Productions: Hunt Shoot - D'Aubuisson in Wash. DC #1, 1984 June 27 (Box 2)
  - Delta Productions: Hunt Shoot - D'Aubuisson in Wash. DC #2, 1984 June 27 (Box 2)
  - Delta Productions: Hunt Shoot - D'Aubuisson in Wash. DC #3, 1984 June 28 (Box 2)
  - Delta Productions: Hunt Shoot - D'Aubuisson in Wash. DC #4, 1984 June 28 (Box 3)
  - Delta Productions: Hunt Shoot - D'Aubuisson in Wash. DC #5, 1984 June 28 (Box 3)
  - Jim Hunt 7/2/-7/10, 1984 July (Box 3)
  - Hunt/Helms - Sun. Morn. Better Copy - Nazi Salute, 1984 July 1 (Box 3)
  - News for Sawyer, 1984 July (Box 3)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-120, "Map", 1984 July 6 (Box 3)
  - Bob Windsor Press Conference, 1984 July 7 (Box 3)
  - Moyers 7/11/84, J.T. Knott :30 #408 (Original), 1984 July 11 (Box 3)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-121, "Dream;" JHSEN-122, "Kitty Hawk;" JHSEN-123, "America;" JHSEN-124, "1976", 1984 July 12 (Box 3)
  - Jesse Jackson, 1984 July 17 (Box 3)
  - Hunt/Helms Debate Original (M.D.), 1984 July 24 (Box 3)
  - VPA Demo Tape, 1984 July 28 (Box 3)
  - Hunt/Helms?Debate #1, 1984 July 29 (Box 3)
  - Hunt/Helms, 1984 July 29 (Box 3)
  - Sawyer Tape, August News Clips, 1984 August 1 (Box 3)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-125, "Stay Tuned", 1984 August 6 (Box 3)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-127, "North Carolina;" JHSEN-128, "Voting for Kids;" JHSEN-129, "N.C. Democrat", 1984 August 15 (Box 3)
  - Hunt: Andy Griffith Shoot Footage, 1984 August 22 (Box 3)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-130, "Richardson Preyer", 1984 August 27 (Box 3)
  - Hunt Compilation for DHS, September '84, 1984 September 1 (Box 3)
  - Hunt-Helms Debate III, Hunt-Helms Debate IV, 1984 September-October (Box 3)
  - Sawyer Dub - Helms-Hunt Coverage September 16 - October 3, 1984 September-October (Box 3)
  - Helms - National Governors Association, 1984 September 4 (Box 3)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-133, "Working Woman", 1984 September 4 (Box 3)
  - Hunt/Helms Debate, 1984 September 9 (Box 3)
  - Hunt/Helms Debate, 1984 September 9 (Box 3)
  - Hunt Helms Debate, 1984 September 9 (Box 3)
  - Hunt Helms Debate, 1984 September 9 (Box 3)
  - Hunt/Helms Debate 09/09/1984, 1984 September 9 (Box 3)
  - Helms Spots, 1984 September 10 (Box 3)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-138, "It's People", 1984 September 21 (Box 4)
  - Hunt/Helms, 1984 September 23 (Box 4)
  - Hunt/Helms III, 1984 September 23 (Box 4)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-139, "Drawing;" JHSEN-140, "Doesn't Jesse Understand?", 1984 September 24 (Box 4)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-131, "Training for the Future;" JHSEN-132, "Parents", 1984 September 29 (Box 4)
  - Hunt Helms to Sawyer, 1984 October 1 (Box 4)
  - Sawyer Dub - Hunt-Helms 10/84, 1984 October 1 (Box 4)
  - Jim Hunt Committee, 1984 October 5 (Box 4)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-145, "They Win;" JHSEN-146, "He Will;" JHSEN-147, "Can't Run", 1984 October 6 (Box 4)
  - Gov. Hunt, 1984 October 8 (Box 4)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-150, "It's Not North Carolina/A Roll", 1984 October 12 (Box 4)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-145, "They Win;" JHSEN-150, "It's Not North Carolina;" JHSEN-148, "What They Want;" JHSEN-149, "What Do You Think;" People for the American Way: "Woman in Rocking Chair;" "Man in Study", 1984 October 12 (Box 4)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-145, "They Win;" JHSEN-150, "It's Not North Carolina;" JHSEN-148, "What They Want;" JHSEN-149, "What Do You Think;" People for the American Way: "Woman in Rocking Chair;" "Man in Study", 1984 October 12 (Box 4)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-150, "It's Not North Carolina/B Roll and Work Pix", 1984 October 13 (Box 4)
  - Hunt Helms debate, 1984 October 13 (Box 4)
  - Hunt Testimonials, 1984 October 15 (Box 7)
  - McNeil-Lehrer 6PM, 1984 October 16 (Box 4)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-151, "Priorities;" JHSEN-152, "Alternate Priorities", 1984 October 16 (Box 4)
  - Gov. Hunt, 1984 October 18 (Box 4)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-153, "Campaign;" JHSEN-154, "Different View", 1984 October 18 (Box 4)
  - NGA (National Governors Association?) Misery / Helms Ad, 1984 October 18 (Box 4)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-155, "Progress" Film Xfer, 1984 October 19 (Box 4)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-155, "Progress", 1984 October 20 (Box 4)
  - Begin news, 1984 October 23 (Box 5)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-158, "We Can Do Anything", 1984 October 24 (Box 5)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-158, "We Can Do Anything", 1984 October 24 (Box 5)
  - Too Liberal, Americans for Reagan, Helms for Senate, 1984 October 24 (Box 5)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-157, "Wrenn and Ellis;" JHSEN-158, "Nothing Can Stop Us;" JHSEN-154, "Different View", 1984 October 24 (Box 5)
  - Burn Code, Hunt Testimonials, 1984 October 25 (Box 5)
  - Jesse Helms on FEC Investigation, 1984 October 25 (Box 5)
  - Falwell 20, 1984 October 26 (Box 5)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-159, "Debate", 1984 October 29 (Box 5)
  - Hunt, 1984 October 30 (Box 5)
  - Hunt, 1984 October 30 (Box 5)
  - Hunt 10/30/84, 1984 October 30 (Box 5)
  - Hunt 10-30-84, 1984 October 30 (Box 5)
  - Hunt 10-30-84, 1984 October 30 (Box 5)
  - Hunt Testimonial, 1984 October 30 (Box 5)
  - Hunt Testimonials, 1984 October 30 (Box 5)
  - Hunt Testimonials, 1984 October 30 (Box 5)
  - Hunt Testimonials, 1984 October 30 (Box 5)
  - Hunt Testimonials, 1984 October 30 (Box 5)
  - Hunt Testimonials, 1984 October 30 (Box 5)
  - Hunt Testimonials R-1, 1984 October 30 (Box 5)
  - Hunt Testimonials R-3, 1984 October 30 (Box 5)
  - Hunt Testimonials R-8, 1984 October 30 (Box 6)
  - Hunt Testimonials R-9, 1984 October 30 (Box 6)
  - Hunt Testiomonials R-7, 1984 October 30 (Box 6)
  - Hunt, 1984 October 30 (Box 6)
  - Hunt, 1984 October 30 (Box 6)
  - Hunt Testimonials, 1984 October 30 (Box 6)
  - Hunt Testimonials, 1984 October 30 (Box 6)
  - Hunt Testimonials, 1984 October 30 (Box 6)
  - Hunt Reel 1 of 4: Sheriff John Baker, Phebe Emmons (social security), Leo Jenkins, 1984 October 30 (Box 6)
  - Hunt Reel 2 of 4: Leo Jenkins (cont.), Dr. Marse Grant, Liz Hair, Cong. Charles Whitely, 1984 October 30 (Box 6)
  - Hunt Reel 3 of 4: Smedes York, Jay Robinson, Dan Moore, Susan Nichols, 1984 October 30 (Box 6)
  - Hunt Reel 4 of 4: Susan Nichols (cont.), 1984 October 30 (Box 6)
  - Friends of Jesse / Fund for a Conservative Majority, 1984 October 30 (Box 6)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-160, "Debate Rev", 1984 October 30 (Box 6)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-161, "Time", 1984 October 31 (Box 6)
  - Hunt: Selects, F/T, 1984 November 1 (Box 7)
  - Hunt Interview, 1984 November 1 (Box 8)
  - Hunt Selects, 1984 November 1 (Box 8)
  - Hunt: Exteriors: North Carolina, Interviews: Brad Miller and Jim Hunt, 1984 November 2 (Box 7)
  - DHS Film: Jim Hunt Interview, 1984 November 2 (Box 7)
  - Bump Up News Footage Reel 2, 1984 November 2 (Box 8)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-162, "Countdown '84", 1984 November 2 (Box 8)
  - Hunt: JHSEN-162, "Countdown '84", 1984 November 2 (Box 23)
  - Day after election news, 1984 November 7 (Box 8)
  - Day after election news, 1984 November 7 (Box 8)
  - Emerging Issues Forum, 1987 (Box 10)
  - Gardner Rand Debate 88 Lt. Governor Race, 1988 (Box 22)
  - Gardner Rand Debate 88 Lt. Governor Race, 1988 (Box 22)
  - Charlotte Focus Groups, 1989 November 21 (Box 10)
  - John Engler -- "And his Mom," 1990 Governor's Race -- Michigan (Box 21)
  - C-Span NBPTS S.695, 1990 February 7 (Box 10)
  - C-Span NBPTS S.695, 1990 February 7 (Box 10)
  - C-Span NBPTS S.695, 1990 February 7 (Box 10)
  - Vance-Aycock Forum Prep, 1991 October 7 (Box 10)
  - Vance-Aycock Forum Prep, 1991 October 7 (Box 10)
  - Vance-Aycock Candidates Forum, 1991 October 12 (Box 10)
  - Gardner Ads, 1991-1992 (Box 20)
  - Jim Gardner Committee 1992 Television (Box 16)
  - Media Prep Session for World Class Schools Forum, 1992 January 8 (Box 10)
  - World Class Schools Forum, 1992 January 11 (Box 10)
  - Sanford House Parties Video, 1992 January 21 (Box 10)
  - Gardner Announcement Speech, 1992 January 30 (Box 10)
  - Gardner Announcement Speech, 1992 January 30 (Box 10)
  - Jim Hunt announces candidacy, Jim Gardner announces candidacy, WTVD, 1992 February 1 (Box 22)
  - Dubbed News Coverage (Announcement), WRAl, WTVD, WWAY, WXII, WFMY, WCHP, WSOC, WCNC, WITN, 1992 February 25 (Box 10)
  - Hunt Announcement Speech, Listen and Learn, 1992 February 25 (Box 10)
  - WECT News 6:00 + 11:00, 1992 February 25 (Box 10)
  - WRAL-TV5, News - Announcement Day (Hunt & Gardner), 1992 February 25 (Box 10)
  - WITN-TV, 6PM and 11PM News, 1992 February 25 (Box 22)
  - World Class Schools Forum (Televised Broadcast) Sheraton Imperial - RTP, 1992 March 1 (Box 10)
  - WCII-TV12 Interview, 1992 March 26 (Box 10)
  - WITN News 11PM, 1992 March 26 (Box 10)
  - Hunt for Governor, "Challenge," "Education," "Jobs," "Testimonial I," "Testimonial II", 1992 March 31 (Box 10)
  - Hunt for Governor, "Challenge," "Education," "Jobs," "Testimonial I," "Testimonial II", 1992 March 31 (Box 10)
  - Hunt for Governor: "Challenge," "Education," "Jobs," "Testimonial", 1992 April 1 (Box 10)
  - WTVD 5:30, 11:00 News, Stories on Independent article on Gardner's business record -stories only- *for focus group, 1992 April 1 (Box 10)
  - WTVD 5:30, 6:00, 11:00 News, Stories on Independent article on Gardner's business record, 1992 April 1 (Box 10)
  - WTVD Report on the Independent Gardner article 5:30 news, 1992 April 1 (Box 10)
  - Hickman/Brown L&E Research, 1992 April 7 (Box 10)
  - Hickman/Brown L&E Research, 1992 April 7 (Box 10)
  - Focus Group Equifax - Quick Test, 1992 April 8 (Box 10)
  - Focus Group Equifax - Quick Test, 1992 April 8 (Box 10)
  - 1)Gubernatorial Forum - Jefferson-Jackson YD Forum (Incomplete) (Introductions, Opening Remarks, Q's from Floor) (N. Ral. Hilt.) 2)WRAL/SOS Gubernatorial Debate on the Environment (Hooper, Mavretic, Thornburg, Williams) (Kerr-Scott Building), 1992 April 11 (Box 10)
  - Hunt Press Briefing on Economic Development Plan, NC Democratic Party HQ, 1992 April 13 (Box 10)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-109, "Together", 1992 April 14 (Box 10)
  - NC Center for Public Television Democratic Party Debate, 1992 April 14 (Box 10)
  - UNC Center for Public TV Debate Prep Session, Poyner & Spruill, 1992 April 14 (Box 11)
  - NC Association of Independent Colleges and Universities, Democratic and Republican Candidates for Governor, Forum at Mid-Pines, 1992 April 15 (Box 11)
  - Hunt for Governor: JM-101, "Challenge", 1992 April 17 (Box 11)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-110, "Education 2", 1992 April 17 (Box 11)
  - Hunt for Governor, "Challenge II" ROUGH CUT, 1992 April 21 (Box 11)
  - Hunt for Governor: JH-111, "Courage", 1992 April 23 (Box 11)
  - WTVD Debate/Town Hall Prep, 4/24/92, 1992 April 24 (Box 11)
  - Hunt for Governor, "WTVD Town Hall Meeting Debate 4/25/92", 1992 April 25 (Box 11)
  - Hunt for Governor, "WTVD Town Hall Meeting Debate 4/25/92", 1992 April 25 (Box 11)
  - WBTV-3/Charlotte 6pm News 5/1/92 (Hunt wins poll/debate), 1992 May 1 (Box 11)
  - WTVD News on Hunt Fly-around, 1992 May 4 (Box 11)
  - WBT/WSOC TV Fly Around Coverage, 1992 May 4 (Box 11)
  - Gardner Primary Election Night Speech, 1992 May 5 (Box 11)
  - WFMY-TV2, Greensboro, 6-7-11 news, Primary Election Cov., 1992 May 5 (Box 11)
  - WGHP-TV8, Greensboro, Greg-Hunt, Election Night, 1992 May 5 (Box 11)
  - WRAL-TV5 11PM News, Primary Election Night, 1992 May 5 (Box 11)
  - WSOC-TV Election Coverage, 1992 May 5 (Box 11)
  - WTVD-TV11 News, Election Night (Primary), 1992 May 5 (Box 11)
  - WFMY-TV2 News 6-7-11 (L. Simpson retract), 1992 May 7 (Box 11)
  - WTVD-CH11 News, 1992 May 20 (Box 11)
  - News Clips, Tape I: 1)WTVD Abortion 6/29; 2)WXII Gardner (Raleigh Parole Ofc.) 7-1-92; 3)NC Rep. Neg Ad "Hunt on Taxes"; 4)WFMY-TV2 Hunt town meeting, 1992 June 1 (Box 11)
  - Wicker-Pope Debate '92, Lt. Gov. Race, 1992 June (Box 20)
  - WFMY-TV2, Business Roundtable Clip, 1992 June 2 (Box 11)
  - North Carolina Business Roundtable? (Greensboro?), 1992 June 4 (Box 22)
  - Debate Prep, 1992 June 21 (Box 11)
  - WXII-TV12: Gardner/Parole ofc./Bond $, 1992 July 1 (Box 11)
  - WFMY-TV2, Hunt Town Meeting, 1992 July 6 (Box 11)
  - Gardner TV Spot, New 60 sec Bio, 1992 July 7 (Box 11)
  - Hunt at Dem. Convention, 1992 July 13 (Box 11)
  - WECT-TV News Clip on NC Rep. Radio Tax as + Hawke Press Conf. on the same, 1992 July 17 (Box 11)
  - Clinton/Gore for President: "The Man from Hope", 1992 July 21 (Box 11)
  - WFMY - MD Poll, 1992 July 24 (Box 11)
  - WRAL-TV5 Hunt Crime News Conference Ral./Gardner reaction to M-D Poll, 6PM, 1992 July 27 (Box 11)
  - WRAL-TV5, Crime Paper Press Conf., Hunt/Hawke/Ballus, 1992 July 27 (Box 11)
  - WGHP-TV8, Crime pkg, Press Conf. + put prisoners to work, 1992 July 27 (Box 11)
  - Crime Paper News Conf. D. PTY Headqtrs., 1992 July 27 (Box 11)
  - WECT-TV, Wilm., 6+11, Ev. Ward/NC Dem Party/NC GOP Ed. Bur. Attack Ad Rebuttal Press Conf., 1992 July 30 (Box 12)